{"problemsArray": [
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 1)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -9, -1 \u0026 9, 3 \u0026 -3, -3 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal 8 are -1 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 8x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -72, -1 \u0026 72, 2 \u0026 -36, -2 \u0026 36, 3 \u0026 -24, -3 \u0026 24, 4 \u0026 -18, -4 \u0026 18, 6 \u0026 -12, -6 \u0026 12, 8 \u0026 -9, -8 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are -8 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 72", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -2, -1 \u0026 2\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are 2 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 4)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 28, -1 \u0026 -28, 2 \u0026 14, -2 \u0026 -14, 4 \u0026 7, -4 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -11 are -4 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 11x + 28", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 7)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 7, -1 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -8 are -7 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 8x + 7", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -12, -1 \u0026 12, 2 \u0026 -6, -2 \u0026 6, 3 \u0026 -4, -3 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are 2 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x - 12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -56, -1 \u0026 56, 2 \u0026 -28, -2 \u0026 28, 4 \u0026 -14, -4 \u0026 14, 7 \u0026 -8, -7 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are -8 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 56", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 6)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 18, -1 \u0026 -18, 2 \u0026 9, -2 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 6, -3 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal 9 are 6 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 9x + 18", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 9)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -27, -1 \u0026 27, 3 \u0026 -9, -3 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal -6 are -9 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 6x - 27", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 5)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -45, -1 \u0026 45, 3 \u0026 -15, -3 \u0026 15, 5 \u0026 -9, -5 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are 5 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x - 45", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 4, -1 \u0026 -4, 2 \u0026 2, -2 \u0026 -2\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 4 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 8)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 16, -1 \u0026 -16, 2 \u0026 8, -2 \u0026 -8, 4 \u0026 4, -4 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 10 are 8 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 10x + 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 9, -1 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 3, -3 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 10 are 9 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 10x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -28, -1 \u0026 28, 2 \u0026 -14, -2 \u0026 14, 4 \u0026 -7, -4 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are 7 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 28", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -8, -1 \u0026 8, 2 \u0026 -4, -2 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are -4 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -40, -1 \u0026 40, 2 \u0026 -20, -2 \u0026 20, 4 \u0026 -10, -4 \u0026 10, 5 \u0026 -8, -5 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal -3 are -8 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 3x - 40", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 2)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are -2 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 8)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 8, -1 \u0026 -8, 2 \u0026 4, -2 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 9 are 8 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 9x + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 1)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 1, -1 \u0026 -1\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are -1 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 5)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 25, -1 \u0026 -25, 5 \u0026 5, -5 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal 10 are 5 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 10x + 25", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are -3 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -27, -1 \u0026 27, 3 \u0026 -9, -3 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal -6 are 3 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 6x - 27", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 5)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -5, -1 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are 5 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x - 5", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 27, -1 \u0026 -27, 3 \u0026 9, -3 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -3 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 27", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 1)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -9, -1 \u0026 9, 3 \u0026 -3, -3 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal 8 are -1 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 8x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -32, -1 \u0026 32, 2 \u0026 -16, -2 \u0026 16, 4 \u0026 -8, -4 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are -8 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x - 32", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 7)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -42, -1 \u0026 42, 2 \u0026 -21, -2 \u0026 21, 3 \u0026 -14, -3 \u0026 14, 6 \u0026 -7, -6 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are -7 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 42", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 7)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 28, -1 \u0026 -28, 2 \u0026 14, -2 \u0026 -14, 4 \u0026 7, -4 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 11 are 7 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 11x + 28", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 5)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -15, -1 \u0026 15, 3 \u0026 -5, -3 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are -5 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 15", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 5)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -40, -1 \u0026 40, 2 \u0026 -20, -2 \u0026 20, 4 \u0026 -10, -4 \u0026 10, 5 \u0026 -8, -5 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are -5 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 40", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 9)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 81, -1 \u0026 -81, 3 \u0026 27, -3 \u0026 -27, 9 \u0026 9, -9 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -18 are -9 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 18x + 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -30, -1 \u0026 30, 2 \u0026 -15, -2 \u0026 15, 3 \u0026 -10, -3 \u0026 10, 5 \u0026 -6, -5 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are -6 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 30", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -21, -1 \u0026 21, 3 \u0026 -7, -3 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are 3 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x - 21", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 9)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 45, -1 \u0026 -45, 3 \u0026 15, -3 \u0026 -15, 5 \u0026 9, -5 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -14 are -9 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 14x + 45", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 1)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -7 are -1 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 7x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 2)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -10, -1 \u0026 10, 2 \u0026 -5, -2 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are -2 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 16, -1 \u0026 -16, 2 \u0026 8, -2 \u0026 -8, 4 \u0026 4, -4 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 10 are 2 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 10x + 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 9, -1 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 3, -3 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are 3 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 36, -1 \u0026 -36, 2 \u0026 18, -2 \u0026 -18, 3 \u0026 12, -3 \u0026 -12, 4 \u0026 9, -4 \u0026 -9, 6 \u0026 6, -6 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -6 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 7)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -42, -1 \u0026 42, 2 \u0026 -21, -2 \u0026 21, 3 \u0026 -14, -3 \u0026 14, 6 \u0026 -7, -6 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are -7 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 42", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 8)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -24, -1 \u0026 24, 2 \u0026 -12, -2 \u0026 12, 3 \u0026 -8, -3 \u0026 8, 4 \u0026 -6, -4 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 8 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x - 24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -4, -1 \u0026 4, 2 \u0026 -2, -2 \u0026 2\nThe two factors that add to equal -3 are -4 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 3x - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -14, -1 \u0026 14, 2 \u0026 -7, -2 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are 2 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x - 14", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -8, -1 \u0026 8, 2 \u0026 -4, -2 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal 2 are 4 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 2x - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 18, -1 \u0026 -18, 2 \u0026 9, -2 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 6, -3 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal -9 are -3 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9x + 18", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 24, -1 \u0026 -24, 2 \u0026 12, -2 \u0026 -12, 3 \u0026 8, -3 \u0026 -8, 4 \u0026 6, -4 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal -11 are -8 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 11x + 24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -6, -1 \u0026 6, 2 \u0026 -3, -2 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are 3 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -7, -1 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are 7 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x - 7", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 6)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 36, -1 \u0026 -36, 2 \u0026 18, -2 \u0026 -18, 3 \u0026 12, -3 \u0026 -12, 4 \u0026 9, -4 \u0026 -9, 6 \u0026 6, -6 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal 12 are 6 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 12x + 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 9, -1 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 3, -3 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -6 are -3 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 6x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -54, -1 \u0026 54, 2 \u0026 -27, -2 \u0026 27, 3 \u0026 -18, -3 \u0026 18, 6 \u0026 -9, -6 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are 9 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 54", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 32, -1 \u0026 -32, 2 \u0026 16, -2 \u0026 -16, 4 \u0026 8, -4 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -8 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 32", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 8, -1 \u0026 -8, 2 \u0026 4, -2 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are 4 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 2)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 10, -1 \u0026 -10, 2 \u0026 5, -2 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal -7 are -2 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 7x + 10", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -4, -1 \u0026 4, 2 \u0026 -2, -2 \u0026 2\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are -1 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 3, -1 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are -3 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x + 3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 4, -1 \u0026 -4, 2 \u0026 2, -2 \u0026 -2\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 4 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 12, -1 \u0026 -12, 2 \u0026 6, -2 \u0026 -6, 3 \u0026 4, -3 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal -8 are -6 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 8x + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 36, -1 \u0026 -36, 2 \u0026 18, -2 \u0026 -18, 3 \u0026 12, -3 \u0026 -12, 4 \u0026 9, -4 \u0026 -9, 6 \u0026 6, -6 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -6 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 2 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 1)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 9, -1 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 3, -3 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -10 are -1 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 10x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 4, -1 \u0026 -4, 2 \u0026 2, -2 \u0026 -2\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 4 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 8)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 64, -1 \u0026 -64, 2 \u0026 32, -2 \u0026 -32, 4 \u0026 16, -4 \u0026 -16, 8 \u0026 8, -8 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal 16 are 8 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 16x + 64", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -1, -1 \u0026 1\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are 1 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 1)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 9, -1 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 3, -3 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 10 are 1 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 10x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -2, -1 \u0026 2\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are 2 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 7)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -28, -1 \u0026 28, 2 \u0026 -14, -2 \u0026 14, 4 \u0026 -7, -4 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal -3 are -7 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 3x - 28", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 2)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are -2 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 5)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -20, -1 \u0026 20, 2 \u0026 -10, -2 \u0026 10, 4 \u0026 -5, -4 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are 5 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 20", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 7)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 7, -1 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 8 are 7 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 8x + 7", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -24, -1 \u0026 24, 2 \u0026 -12, -2 \u0026 12, 3 \u0026 -8, -3 \u0026 8, 4 \u0026 -6, -4 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are -6 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -81, -1 \u0026 81, 3 \u0026 -27, -3 \u0026 27, 9 \u0026 -9, -9 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are 9 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -6, -1 \u0026 6, 2 \u0026 -3, -2 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are -3 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 12, -1 \u0026 -12, 2 \u0026 6, -2 \u0026 -6, 3 \u0026 4, -3 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal -8 are -6 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 8x + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -24, -1 \u0026 24, 2 \u0026 -12, -2 \u0026 12, 3 \u0026 -8, -3 \u0026 8, 4 \u0026 -6, -4 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are -6 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 24", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -32, -1 \u0026 32, 2 \u0026 -16, -2 \u0026 16, 4 \u0026 -8, -4 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are -8 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x - 32", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 8)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 16, -1 \u0026 -16, 2 \u0026 8, -2 \u0026 -8, 4 \u0026 4, -4 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 10 are 8 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 10x + 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 1)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -9, -1 \u0026 9, 3 \u0026 -3, -3 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal 8 are -1 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 8x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 21, -1 \u0026 -21, 3 \u0026 7, -3 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -10 are -3 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 10x + 21", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -72, -1 \u0026 72, 2 \u0026 -36, -2 \u0026 36, 3 \u0026 -24, -3 \u0026 24, 4 \u0026 -18, -4 \u0026 18, 6 \u0026 -12, -6 \u0026 12, 8 \u0026 -9, -8 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are -8 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 72", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 28, -1 \u0026 -28, 2 \u0026 14, -2 \u0026 -14, 4 \u0026 7, -4 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 11 are 4 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 11x + 28", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 18, -1 \u0026 -18, 2 \u0026 9, -2 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 6, -3 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal 11 are 2 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 11x + 18", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -28, -1 \u0026 28, 2 \u0026 -14, -2 \u0026 14, 4 \u0026 -7, -4 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are -4 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 28", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 9, -1 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 3, -3 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -6 are -3 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 6x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 54, -1 \u0026 -54, 2 \u0026 27, -2 \u0026 -27, 3 \u0026 18, -3 \u0026 -18, 6 \u0026 9, -6 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal 15 are 9 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 15x + 54", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 2)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -8, -1 \u0026 8, 2 \u0026 -4, -2 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal 2 are -2 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 2x - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -36, -1 \u0026 36, 2 \u0026 -18, -2 \u0026 18, 3 \u0026 -12, -3 \u0026 12, 4 \u0026 -9, -4 \u0026 9, 6 \u0026 -6, -6 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are 4 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 7)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 42, -1 \u0026 -42, 2 \u0026 21, -2 \u0026 -21, 3 \u0026 14, -3 \u0026 -14, 6 \u0026 7, -6 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -13 are -7 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 13x + 42", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 10, -1 \u0026 -10, 2 \u0026 5, -2 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal 7 are 5 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 7x + 10", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -8, -1 \u0026 8, 2 \u0026 -4, -2 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are 2 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 5)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -20, -1 \u0026 20, 2 \u0026 -10, -2 \u0026 10, 4 \u0026 -5, -4 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are -5 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 20", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 6)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 7 are 6 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 7x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 9, -1 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 3, -3 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are 3 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 8)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -16, -1 \u0026 16, 2 \u0026 -8, -2 \u0026 8, 4 \u0026 -4, -4 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are 8 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x - 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 42, -1 \u0026 -42, 2 \u0026 21, -2 \u0026 -21, 3 \u0026 14, -3 \u0026 -14, 6 \u0026 7, -6 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -13 are -6 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 13x + 42", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 8, -1 \u0026 -8, 2 \u0026 4, -2 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal -9 are -8 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9x + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -42, -1 \u0026 42, 2 \u0026 -21, -2 \u0026 21, 3 \u0026 -14, -3 \u0026 14, 6 \u0026 -7, -6 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are 7 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 42", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x + 6)(x - 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -48, -1 \u0026 48, 2 \u0026 -24, -2 \u0026 24, 3 \u0026 -16, -3 \u0026 16, 4 \u0026 -12, -4 \u0026 12, 6 \u0026 -8, -6 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are 6 and -8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 48", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 27, -1 \u0026 -27, 3 \u0026 9, -3 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -3 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 27", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 3)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 3)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 3)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 3)"], "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -27, -1 \u0026 27, 3 \u0026 -9, -3 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are -3 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x - 27", "type": "text"}
]}